Mystery Science Theater 3000 Show 416, real one.
In the not too distant future, next Sunday A.D.
There was a guy named Joe, not too different from you or me.
He worked at Gizmonic Institute, just another face in a red gel suit.
He did a good job cleaning up the place, but his boss is getting like him so they shot him into space.
We'll send him cheesy movies, the worst we can find.
He'll have to sit and watch them all and the monitor is mine.
Now keep in mind, Joe can't control where the movies begin or end.
Because he used those special parts to make his robot friends.
Robot, cool, cool, camo, gypsy, Tom Servo, crow.
You're wondering how he eats and breathes and other science facts.
Then repeat to yourself, it's just a show.
I should really just relax for Mystery Science Theater 3000.
(
Hi everybody, welcome to the satellite of love, I'm Joe Robinson.
I was just teaching the bots here about proper posture.
You know what a stickler I am? Stick around, we're just about to crown the king and queen of posture.
Yeah, Joe, about this whole king and queen thing, couldn't there be like a baron and duke of posture instead?
Or if you like, a dauphin of posture?
I was thinking maybe I could just marry into posture.
You're clowning, okay. You know Tom Servo, your posture is exemplary.
Did anybody ever tell you you kind of look like a gumball machine from the side?
Is that so? I hadn't realized.
Okay, check me, check me.
Crow, we checked you already. Come on you guys, let's get out of here. It's time for the big coronation.
Ah, forget the crowns.
Who are you? What are you doing here? Keep away. Keep on clowning.
Hey, anybody know what happened to Cam Bot?
Not me. Not me.
Yeah, right. We'll quit riffing on family circus you two, alright. Hey, who's this over here?
Oh, I prayed for a friend and he came. His name is Timmy.
Well, I thought you wanted a bike.
Crow, allow me to play devil's advocate here. Isn't that rather preternatural?
Listen, we'll deal with this later. Differ and Tillbrook are calling.
Hello gang of four. We racked Frank's brain for this week's invention exchange, but nothing doing.
Then I realized it was right under our noses. Frankie Poole?
Frank!
Well, let's say the Kiwanis want to present a check to the local cheerleaders for their brand new uniforms.
So they want to end up on the front page of the Pope County Trumpeter with this puny check?
No, you'll need the big check from the big checkbook. That's right, Daddy's got the checkbook for Wimbledon, Publishers Clearing House, Shriners Hospital, PGA Tours.
They all have to come to me, because Forester cuts the checks.
Daddy Warbucks Forester holds all the cards.
Doctor, doctor, I have this Volvo called. My guest, Courier, won the tournament and they need a check for $400,000.
Well, don't just stand there, Frank. Cut them a check.
Okay, sure.
Volvo. V-O... What's the date?
Frank, there's a couple of checks missing here.
I guess I wrote a couple.
To whom, Frank? To whom?
Oh, uh...
Think?
No.
Frank, you've got to remember to register the checks!
Jerry's Kids. That's it, Jerry's Kids. Does 1.5 mil make any sense?
Why don't you go on with your invention exchange, Mr. Roper?
Today's invention exchange is a new kind of sneaker technology.
You've got your air sneakers and you've got your gel sneakers, but what good are either of them if you can't eat them?
The centerpiece of this high-tech cross-training shoe is a shock-resistant chamber of deliciously spreadable port wine cheese,
which provides cushioning to the heel and gentle arch support at three crucial impact points.
And, oh, it's great on crackers. Say you just finished a grueling 10K.
You park your hinder at the juice bar and what do they serve you? A piece of rye crisp.
May we suggest you top it with rich, creamery cheese?
Right. The Nike Arch-lotted. Just eat it.
Is that cheese or is that the shoe? What do you think, sirs?
Think, Frank, think! I don't know.
Do you know what this means? It means bankruptcy and scandal in prison.
One of us is going to prison and it ain't gonna be me!
Your experiment this week, Joel, is a Cyroth classic called "Fire Maidens of Outer Space."
Frank, did you buy any little donuts you like? Did you rent any movies? Did you get any Time Live books?
Think, man, think! I don't.
No way, Cro. Timmy can't come into the theater with us.
Oh, no! We got movie time!
I'm pretty sure it was the cheese. Yeah.
Hey! Coming into Los Alamos, bringing in some cadmium rods.
Yes, Los Alamos fly Alamogordo Airlines.
Oh, I bet George Kennedy's in this.
Oh, New York, right? By the time that plane lands, it'll be covered with graffiti.
Mr. Secretary, the next sound you will hear will be a high-pitched squeal.
That'll be the sound of the ambassador's phone melting.
Cyroth, maker of films and fine candies.
Anthony. Dexter. Susan. Shaw.
Oh.
I am the maiden of Hellfire.
Fire maidens really grip the road.
I wonder if they're volunteer fire maidens.
And introducing Jacqueline Curtis.
Mya cumani, my darling.
And the skating fire maidens.
I'm bored already.
Oh, let's bring him out again. Cyroth, ladies and gentlemen. All right.
Hey, me and Struthers and Scott McGregor here on the old course at St. Andrews.
Prince Eager Borredin? Isn't it Prince Rogers Nelson?
You know, I really don't care. I've gotten to the point where I really don't care.
Oh, yeah. Just in case you forgot, directed by Cy-Roth.
You know, even Quinn Martin was a Cy-Roth production.
In the mutual interests of peace and security for all mankind,
There is no smoking.
The great nations of the United States and Great Britain had been working on a secret project designated 13.
The operation on plan 13 was completed and the top nuclear scientist of the United States is tired.
The joint operation.
Say, this is a joint operation.
To join his British colleagues and head plan 13.
An expedition that will live in infamy.
So I'm a briefcase. What do you do for a living?
Oh, no, they're bombing Levittown.
Outer space in a prop plane? I don't think so.
Bring it in.
It's the Beatles.
It's been a hard day.
Kind of looks like a Snoopy plane. Friendly dog phaser.
Please remain seated until the movie grinds to a complete halt.
May I have your attention, please?
Welcome to London, ma'am.
Announces the arrival of its eastbound ambassador flight number 100.
Arriving at gate 5, New York and...
Yep, this is London, pretty much.
Can't believe how much I'm in London.
Really, really London.
Have a good trip?
The car's right here.
May I take your gym bag?
Welcome to Burbank, England, jolly old chap.
Hey, it's a clown car.
Hand me that steering wheel, I'll drive.
On the left, on the left, dickweed!
This is not Spoda, Wisconsin, it's still London.
Keep left, darn labor party.
You know, maybe it's just Canada pretending to be England.
It happens.
Keep left, on the left, dickweed!
Hi.
Let's get you right out to the suburbs where it's safe.
You know, this music makes me think they're driving to something really, really grim.
What are they, driving to Scotland?
London Cemetery and Observatory?
Looks like a silo.
The big, big trailer!
Oh yes, red rings.
Yes, smooth.
Celestial body.
I'm going to call it Planet Me.
This confirms your original theory, Dr. Higgins.
And that's why I said come to England at once.
We've known all along that the planet Jupiter has 12 moons.
But evidently terrestrial fogs surrounds the 13th moon most of the time.
Oh, it's not fog, it's your pipe smoke.
Thanks to this new telescope.
Did you get the same impression as I did about this new moon?
Yeah, it's so shy, it never talks.
It appears it looked like the Earth. It does.
It did.
Hey, there's traffic in space.
What do you know?
The colors are similar.
Have they been checked?
Oh yeah, yeah. Here are the results.
Yeah, it's on this piece of Laffy Taffy.
Here.
Think they should have built the observatory and the bus station? Bad idea.
Spectrograph reports indicate atmosphere similar to ours.
Yeah.
All right.
The final tests on the nuclear power engines have been completed.
Good.
I have often walked.
I'm Gary Owens from beautiful downtown Burbank.
How would I put us in a juxtaposition with the 13th moon?
Let's see, a $1.25 for the cigarettes and total that.
Well, if we could be ready to leave within a week,
we'll be in time for the shortest possible journey.
What's your latest estimation?
Twelve.
Once we reach outer space, three weeks.
Or I'm not Norman Rockwell.
You know, there could be humans on that planet.
Yeah, there could be dogs, light rail and tofu. What's your point?
You know how I love humans.
You're a scientist. It's probable, but highly doubtful.
Beings? Yes.
The secretary is not the toy one.
And now red in the silent spot. Red's a secretary.
Thank you, that's all.
No, I didn't know you were there. Don't sneak up like that.
Send a message to Captain Larson.
Launching platform, first interplanetary unit, Hounds Point, Surrey.
Er, ship must be ready one week from today.
Have laundered your shorts, we'll deliver immediately. Kiss kiss, bunny.
I'll be all right. Be sure to call that message.
Compass Trommy can crowd six bagels, bring home for Emma.
Sure could have used the intercom, but no, I have to come all the way down here.
I was just looking at my legs.
(Muffled sounds)
There she goes, Mrs. Secretary.
Mmm, baby got back.
I'll never do old.
Rowan and Martin.
I don't know how Jupiter's satellite will look anything like her.
Allow me to knee you right in the groin, Bob.
This is under some form of light.
Stand by.
For action.
1944, Peter Monda, Hitler's readies his V-Tools for England.
Attention, this is control tower command to all units.
Stand by for launching.
Count will commence in one minute.
I'm not kidding this time.
Tommy Cash.
Wow, and Bob Crosby.
And there's Peter Ackroyd.
Who's vacuuming? Stop vacuuming.
Sounds like Mariah Carey.
Got big ol' ears there, boy.
And back we go.
(Laughing)
What is this, a Bergman film?
No, Stephen.
I'm Ed Bradley and this is 60 Minutes.
Of padding.
Yeah.
Willa Cather?
I've done things I'm not proud of.
Oh, the secrets I have, ooh.
Should I ask him?
George, do you want to have dinner?
And the old clock on the wall says it's time for the Longines Symphony Hour.
I forgot to add the fabric softener.
See if you can keep the scene going another five minutes.
I'm not wearing any shorts.
Cubby.
Roy.
Lonnie.
Bobby.
Oh, oh.
Yeah, it's the Prerna rocket ship.
Checkerboard fins.
We have A&E documentary.
Tonight on biography, peanut money.
The shiny little surrey with the hounds pouring on top.
Well, we blew that. Maybe we should have researched it.
I'm late. I'm late for a very important date.
Have a Coke. This means you, Doc Face.
That guy's the posture king.
Sergeant Beckwano, if that really is your name.
Your identity cards, please, sir.
Got two for ones on watermelon shooters tonight.
Going to have to stamp your hand.
Have a good time. Go get 'em, Tigers.
Oh, man, can we get our cover charge back?
Yeah, it's Nancy Culp night.
Hey.
We'd like three super-supremes and...
Calling Expedition 13.
Come in 13. Acknowledge.
I don't want to come in. I'm playing.
This is the funniest mission.
Ladies and gentlemen, the interplanetary ship has acknowledged our message.
We should keep in constant contact as long as possible.
So did you see Aguilar last night blow that game?
A lot of people praying for George Bailey.
Oh, they must work for Clinique.
Our control says they're receiving us okay.
Good.
Well, gentlemen, we're now in free flight.
I'm feeling really good.
Everything goes all right. We'll contact Jupiter in three weeks.
Oh, hi. How am I doing?
Oh, you're here. Good to see you.
So long, suckers.
Don't even know we're watching 'em, poor bastards.
Just see that? I'm ten minutes into the stratosphere and my wife's already cheating on me.
It's like looking through the wrong end of a telescope, eh, Doug?
Sort of makes one feel insignificant.
I always wanted a bird's-eye view of the Earth, but this...
The four dullards of the apocalypse.
Hey, I wonder what we'll find on the 13th moon.
Let's talk about that later.
Captain, full power.
Aye, aye, sir.
My boots.
Take it out of fifth.
You can't find 'em, grind 'em.
Turn off the magnetic gyro.
That one gear works for everything.
It's poppycock!
It's fiddle faddle!
Mr. Bulky's gone mad!
If this is comocorn, brace yourself for the peanuts, fellas.
Oh, golly.
Hand is falling control of our situation.
Call it control.
Message from Expedition 13.
They've already blown it.
Come in, 13.
Come in.
Video's heading directly for ship.
Stay in contact.
Repeat. Stay in contact.
Let's all watch it on the speaker.
101, 102, 103.
Where's your power?
Oh, you made me lose count.
Thank you.
Get it out of here.
Oh, sir.
Racing switch on full hit.
Whoa!
Look to this day, young graduates.
It's George Tobias.
I'm coming to terms with my sexuality.
I'm sweaty.
You're denying my womanhood, aren't you all?
You know, I definitely hear a bowling alley.
Hey!
Oops, sorry.
He has a Monty Markham quality about him.
You're cute.
Oh, beat Nick Astor.
Danger past. Repeat.
Danger past.
Resuming course.
Resuming course as planned.
Yeah, so that Aguilera.
He blew two last night.
Man, that ice machine really cools you off.
Man, you are so hip.
It reminds me of my wife when she's mad.
Ha, ha. Make jokes at your wife's expense.
Resume planned flight.
And everyone, hairlines recede.
Grand Forks are bust.
So, is there anything else to do on this ship?
Bumper pools, slot machines?
Why don't we talk anymore?
We've got to help George Bailey.
My father never told me he loved me.
Draw Sparky.
Let's see here.
Ah, 15.
Ah, whatever.
Thrill one of these in there.
Oh, hey, look, there's a lot of crappies hanging at about 12 feet there.
Yeah.
I got a question for you.
Say, Joel, remember those two oily guys leering at the secretary?
Oh, you mean the astronomers?
Oh, yeah. As disgusting pigs, they just weren't that convincing.
Believe you me, Joel, I completely understand being mesmerized by the explicit nature of my unspeakable fantasy.
Mm-hmm. Go on.
But couldn't they come up with anything more suggestive than,
"I wonder if the beings on Jupiter's satellite look anything like her"?
Oh, I know what your problem is. You're talking about a double entendre.
And if you want to sound all sexy and suggestive, it's not really what you say, but how you say it.
Joel, Timmy's worried about servo.
Well, why?
Well, he says he should cut down on the bacon and large sandwiches before he dies.
What? What? Oh, my God, let me hear that little guy.
Hey, Tom, take it easy. Timmy's a guest. He doesn't know any better.
You know, Crow, your friend's kind of quiet. Does he talk?
Oh, he talks. Only I can understand him. He wants to talk through me.
Oh, I see. Well, anyway, with double entendre, you could say just about anything, Tom, like,
"Say, does this TV have a remote? Mm."
Oh, I see. How about, say, check out the arms on this jumpsuit.
Oh, right on.
As far as I know, Lincoln's not president anymore.
She came back from the store with a bag of apples and a loaf of bread.
I got one. If the van's a-rockin', don't come knockin'.
Oh, Crow, that's a little bit more direct than what we were talking about.
Here's one. A grinder in the...
Oh, no. Oh. Well, I'm not saying it. It's Timmy who's saying it.
Well, listen, I think you two better learn how to play with each other, all right?
Say, Joel, we got commercial sound.
And now a word from our sponsor, Pooh!
She's built like a brick shi...
Crow! Showboat. Showboat.
Right, that's out of here. I'll move this.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, my lip!
Let me use those fingers.
Oh, sure. I'd love to get your skin condition.
Drop check.
I question the relevance of this scene.
I question the relevance of every scene.
Ow, my hand! Ow!
Well, we can barely pay the gas bill this month.
Ah, ah, cripes. Anybody know anything about quadratic equations?
-X equals A... -Mommy still on hold?
You're clear. It's odd, but he is a fool!
Yes, I know, but he has the faith of a child.
Oh, missed a spot there.
Guys, we're in for some deep padding.
Hey, it's a wonderful life of yours.
It could be one of those, but...
I like that faith. I like George Bailey.
...in my most fun class.
Shut up.
Check our course.
That's my cue!
Put your pencils down, please.
Bear right, zero, zero, two.
Or so.
I was right! We are heading for the fog clouds.
What about Jupiter and the other twelve moons? Any life on them?
There could be, but Blair believes they're barren.
What about it, Blair?
Based on what we've learned, the possibility of life as we know it
is only on the thirteenth moon. You mean people, too?
Shut up, Dave. I'm talking.
We'll soon know.
Take her down, Skipper. We're in the satellite's atmosphere.
Hey, I'll call the shots.
Gee, her hair smells terrific.
Hey, what do you know, a new shot?
Right, Doc. Let's go down and have a closer look.
It's the land of Terry Queen.
They treat you right.
Mmm.
Folks, you thought there wouldn't be any more of these shots.
Sorry, we got a whole real phone.
Blair, quickly.
Quickly in this film? I don't think so.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Is that from control?
No, this is another frequency.
Out your sight.
It's my stupid brother.
Calling spaceship.
You think they mean us?
My fourth name and destination immediately.
You are under our space control.
Check this. My name's Bob and I'm heading down to T.J. Fuddle Bunkers.
We stopped moving.
Hm? Well, listen, they're getting pulled over.
I know.
Here, just a minute.
Fly me to the moon.
This is Expedition 13 from the planet Earth.
And this is one of our favorite songs.
Five men. Five good men.
Destination, the 13th moon of Jupiter.
Purpose of trip, a friendly scientific exploration.
So lay the heck off.
Is this thing on? Hello?
Proceed on cloth.
Bearing on your compass will be 18017.
Landing field between two mountain ranges.
Benedict's got all the dominoes.
That's the wrong bearing. That'll take us nowhere.
I can hear my heart breaking.
The only explanation I can think of is that their gravitational laws and magnetic poles are contrary to ours.
Seems like there's nothing else to do but follow their instructions.
Count of three, everybody nap.
Expedition 13 proceeding as ordered.
Oh, they're heading for a Van Gogh.
Look at those mountains playing.
Appears to be a flaky crust, sir.
We'd better find a plane soon.
Or at least a place to eat lunch.
Yep, this is gonna take a while.
King dinosaur! That's from King Di- I'm leaving. I'm not lucky.
Get him back here.
We're either protesting or-
Reversing the film, sir.
Well, go on.
Oh, they're riding in a shape for Crazy Rider.
Oh! That's not a very good effect.
There. Hey, it says I'm a red hot lover.
Glad my deodorant is time released.
Basking in the afterglow.
They're having a Montclair moment.
Yes, I know.
Salem does satisfy.
It is a big moment in our lives and in the lives of the world.
I mean the earth.
Can it, Dave. It's what's up front that counts.
But being a scientist, I have the utmost curiosity to know what lies out there.
The utmost urge to smoke a pack or two.
All right.
Stanhope, check the outside atmosphere.
It's okay. I checked it yesterday.
Anderson, contact control.
Bob, slip into that clown suit.
Arrive destination, beginning exploratory phase.
Smoking like fiends.
Expedition 13 to control. Arrive destination, beginning exploratory phase.
Signing you off.
We got a helium leak, sir. It's pretty bad back here.
From the expression on your face, professor,
I'd say you've found that the atmosphere on the 13th moon of Jupiter
is similar to that of the one on earth.
Am I that transparent?
It's a nail right on the head.
Ah, open the hatch.
Yeah, it smells like a wrestling mat in here.
You know, these new Belvedere's really are mild.
Hey, he's shooting us some wrist.
Yeah, the maid will get those.
Hey!
Oh, that's an effect they took some thought.
Look, they got one to a hardware hang.
That's one small tush for a man, one shapely thigh for mankind.
This will be great.
I want to get your expression as you come down the ladder.
Hey!
Don't take a picture of my butt, please.
Oh, don't.
Jupiter, America's dairy land.
Oh, how do you work this thing?
Stay off the moors.
Tom O'Shanter.
Trees, seeing them.
Huh?
Oh, it's a spruce.
Poplar.
Hey, watch it.
How did you like it if we were to get a picture of you?
How did you like it if we picked your app?
Hey, look, Blab.
Hmm.
Hey, there's a keg.
Anderson, can you read the message somebody is sending?
It's like a code of some sort.
It's from the director. It says, "Slow down."
Head for trees at signal.
Well, that's it and all.
Just repeating the same message.
In other words, would you just get over here?
Eat it, Joes. Eat it, Joes.
That must be the signal. Captain, close the hatch.
Well, I'll just take our word for it. The hatch is closed.
All right, let's head for the beacon on the double.
And the FEM 5 go into action.
Run away! Run away!
Hand me the baton. You gotta give me the baton.
Chariots of fire maidens, those chariots of...
I need a cigarette.
I gotta go potty real bad.
Me too. Me three.
Me four. Me five.
Did anybody bring the deep woods off?
You know, when you're in the woods, you... Never mind.
Serpentine! Serpentine!
I think you missed the woods. It's back.
A planet where apes evolved from men?
Some sort of outward bound thing here.
Hey, we're back at the ship. How'd we do that?
Where's the beacon? What about the voices?
What about that little wall we've just been through?
What about long?
A logical explanation for each occurrence, right, Dr. Higgins?
Right, Mr. Blair.
Let's find the beacon first. Spread out.
Can I spread out with someone, sir? I'm scared.
All done.
I just became an art lover.
Yeah, I thought we were supposed to spread out.
Ah, we spread out in your direction.
Pardon us, ma'am.
I think she likes me.
It's real, all right. Looks like a film of some kind.
I haven't seen anything like it before.
Hold it there. That's beautiful.
I'd say the statue is made of bronze.
Then dipped in chocolate.
It's similar to that on our planet.
Reminds me of a lighthouse beacon.
Reminds me of an apple pie.
It's on land instead of water.
Perhaps the plane was once covered by water.
Yeah, that could be the answer.
The officers are standing here.
I'm wondering about that voice we heard on the radio.
When we meet him, I'll get a picture on the Polaroid.
You're just exposed to film, you idiot!
It is a cheese.
We better get back to the ship before it gets dark.
We can return tomorrow.
Could we stop and buy some postcards?
That would be...
Steve, was that you?
Fellas, is it me or do we all look alike?
That's the human voice.
Wow, they are scientists.
Let's not jump to conclusions. It's getting late.
This could be very important.
We may be able to establish the presence of human life on the 13th moon.
Rula Costa!
I thought...
Say what?
Keep screaming! We're following your voice!
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Oh no, they're Kennedys on the planet!
Woman! You can say that again.
Hey, taking pictures and trying to help us.
We're here to explore, not to get involved in something we know nothing about.
What are you, from New York or something?
Fire a warning shot first.
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Circle to the right. Stand, hold view and energy to the left.
Doc, stay here.
Frankenstein?
Okay, I'm out of here. Nothing's worth a bullet.
Donna Douglas?
Oh.
Hi, it was my idea to shoot him.
Hi, I'm quite average looking.
Meryl Streep meets Laura Dern.
Biologically speaking, the forms of life on this planet are unusual, to say the least.
So far, two extremes.
You can have your extremes. Just let me navigate in one direction only.
Geez, it's the planet of the ropers.
Our bearing is zero zero zero.
Now wait but a hurry or we'll lose our charming guide.
And I'm running out of analogies for sex.
Old spies, out!
Splash it on!
Down!
Trying to lose him.
Fire up the grills, girls. Time for man-witches.
What are we doing again? Where are we?
Doctor, you're in charge of the rear guard.
Ah, thank you.
Anderson, Stanhope, we'll stay with you. Captain Larson will come with me.
We don't return in 30 minutes.
The pizza's free.
We'll return the ship and remain there.
Okay.
Oh great, I get to hold his purse.
It's not a purse, it's a satchel.
Right.
Oh, wait a minute. This is a Star Trek set.
Spa. Spa.
Grandpa, are you down here?
Marilyn!
All right, this way. Our specials today are a nice kale sea bass.
Either these drapes go or we do.
This is really something.
I don't know what, but it's something.
Whoa.
Now look at that painting. These fixtures, rugs, electricity.
They can all be yours if the price is right.
It's real.
What the answer to all this is, I don't know.
The answer is retro-beck.
This architecture is a late Minoan period.
Not Minoan, but late Atlantis.
The two periods of...
Fred Mertz! Close your robe.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The two periods of... Fred Mertz! Close your robe.
Welcome, my friends. Welcome to New Atlantis.
A planned community.
How have you arrived safely?
My name is Prossus.
Hi.
The lone male survivor of Atlantis.
If you know what I mean.
She was my mother's mother.
Wow, Grandma was hot.
She's a gentleman.
Well, you've seen enough of Grandma. Have a seat.
Well, they want a golden globe.
Kind of looks like Brian Keith's room in Family Affair.
A thousand questions are on your lips.
Yet to answer, one would take many days and nights.
Hey, they're paneling.
And I guess we shall have eons of time for discussion.
Yeah, great. So you got any chips or beer or something?
We wish to thank you for your hospitality, but don't want to intrude.
Don't concern yourself with small matters.
You speak of New Atlantis, the lost continent.
Not lost.
Here it is in all its splendor, but there are only a few of us left.
(Makes
a
Yeah, sure. How about some beer nuts or little cocktail weenies or...
Here we are safe.
Here you must remain until you've solved the problem of the destruction of the creature.
Oh, uh, look at the time.
What about the other...
No need to go into that right now, Captain.
Let's accept our host's invitation.
You have made me happy.
So very happy.
I'm so...
You are weary after your long flight.
Food and drink will provide the necessary sustenance.
They always do.
Huh?
My daughter, gentlemen. Hestia, Princess of Atlantis.
Hi.
This is Captain Larson. I'm Luther Blair.
Hestia's life belongs to you from now on, Luther Blair.
Oh, no, that's just plain wrong.
It is the law of Atlantis.
Gee, I didn't bring a daughter for you.
Safe at first.
My child, bring food and drink for our guests.
Do this, do that, bring food and drink. I never get a tip.
Our thanks to the Aphrodite, goddess and queen of all Atlantis.
This guy's badly.
I've seen guys like him in the last war.
I know, but we've got to humor him.
What about the gal?
What about her?
Let her humor us.
She's his daughter. I'm Genghis Khan.
I feel normal.
Hey, do I look like I'm going off my rocker?
Watch out, he's coming back.
Viva Las Vegas.
These are my other daughters, gentlemen.
These are colonels.
Before your eyes are the last descendants of Aphrodite.
Well, Father knows best.
New Atlantis must not die.
What's he trying to suggest?
Whatever it is, I'm all for it.
You think he means...
Hey, wait a minute, I'm a happily married man with two grown kids.
Oh, forget that.
Don't let your imagination run wild.
If that old goat starts anything...
Go for the women, not the old goat.
Do you have decaf?
Well, it'll be dee.
I don't feel so good.
Toast, gentlemen.
Your good health.
Ah, toast, yes, toast.
To Melba.
Well, that's an odd taste.
Well, off the wagon again.
[music]
Hey, what you up to here, Chucky?
Well, you know, I was just thinking about Gypsy and how much work she does around the ship.
Hey, ow, crow, would you cut it out?
I didn't do anything.
Oh, yeah, right.
Anyway, I was noticing in today's experiment how they had two levers that controlled everything.
Ow, right in my skull.
Would you stop that?
Joe, I'm not doing anything.
It was Timmy.
Yeah, sure, blame your new friend.
But it's true, he pushed me.
He's mean.
Monkey Shines and Lion Crow.
I think I know someone who needs a time out.
It's not fair.
No.
Yeah, right.
Well, listen, you just have five minutes and you know where to go, all right?
It's not fair.
I suppose you like him better.
I hate you.
Hey, come here, little friend.
Stop going close.
Get comfortable.
That's right.
So I'll finish what I was explaining before I was interrupted.
This thing is called the twin screw universal controller and it's used to control everything.
Well, gee, everything's a lot of stuff, Joe.
Yeah, I'll say it is.
Check it out.
It controls the ship's yaw, the pitch.
It controls the ship's environment.
It controls the temperature.
It controls the lights.
It controls the doors.
It even controls the hex field view screen.
How about that?
Pretty impressive, Joel.
Thanks.
Don't even get me started on it.
It controls people's opinions, emotions, attitudes.
Here, I'll give you an example.
Let's see.
Could you give me a thing or a person that you really, really dislike?
Oh, easy.
Steve Gutenberg.
Okay, Steve Gutenberg.
Hey, Tom, what do you think about Steve Gutenberg?
I think Three Men and a Little Lady was a terrific movie.
Steve Gutenberg is a patriot, a hero, and one of the finest men I have ever known.
See, check it out.
It's great.
It controls the time.
It controls.
It can make supper in a jiffy.
It lifts.
It separates.
It can turn you into a nine-year-old Hindu boy.
It takes a rat and turns it into a delicious.
Timmy, no!
Joel?
No, no, Timmy.
Here, let me.
No, no, honey.
You see what happens when you touch things?
Let me do it.
Honey!
Joel!
I'm trying, Servo.
Now, cut that out.
Timmy, I told you not to touch anything, all right?
Gee, you're a strange little man.
Where did you come from, any of you?
Joel, if you don't mind, I'm cooking here.
I'm beginning to smell delicious.
All right, Tom, just quit goofing around, okay?
Now, Timmy, I want you to go back to Crow's cubicle and tell you feel better, all right?
Hey, Crow, would you come in here?
It's almost movie time, all right?
Whoopee!
Hey, guys, anything wrong?
Oh, my!
It's a tomato all over me.
You know how ridiculous you look?
Get this off of me.
Get it off.
Thank you.
No?
They all look like waitresses at Caesar's Palace.
What do you know?
What's this?
Femme fatales dancing dervishly to tantalize our dynamic duo?
Yep.
Uh-huh, thank you.
Very nice, very nice.
You know, they should try dancing in time to the music.
Oh, so this is what happens at lingerie parties.
Yeah.
I think these are the 15 Vestal Virgins who are headed for the coast.
Man, I miss the earth.
I keep expecting Danny Terrio to pop out somewhere.
Ladies, this is no drill.
We have real light astronauts this time.
You know, I was just thinking Aphrodite must have lost her shape after a few hundred daughters.
Oh, sure, I didn't make the cut.
Just wait till you open your locker on Monday.
Oh, wow.
I see London.
I see France.
Watching underoos is fun.
I can see the dancers' buns.
Hey, watch this. Give me a dollar.
That's an ashtray, Tom.
Waiter.
Ah, forget it.
Oh, jeez, you didn't have to walk through the middle of the dance.
Can we get a table closer to the plot?
Mm-hmm. Very nice. One grief and earn.
Is that John Cryer back there?
Jeez, how long does this go on?
There's more action in the wallpaper.
Come on, wake up. The show's not over.
I'm taking these two snookums up to bed.
No, I'm a priest. I won't. No. Oh, maybe.
You know, I can feel sex all around us.
Let's go in after them.
No, we're heading back for the ship right now.
What about Blair and Lawson in there?
I bet they're getting totally lucky.
Let's go.
Pina Munda.
Yeah, Mom, I know I never called.
I can't get through.
We've had no word since their last message that they'd started the exploratory phase.
Well, you don't call Jupiter with friends and family for crying out loud.
Just stay in contact and keep sending your message.
All right.
Almighty bomb. Well, that was a bust. Ten minutes on this planet.
The Great Carilou.
We'll wait till morning. Inside it'll be safer.
Come on, we've got lots of interior shots we've got to use up.
Three-course dinner.
Guys, we've been robbed. The stereo's gone.
Hey, look, it's a quarter to something.
Madison, contact control.
All right, boys, what did we learn?
We want to check over our supplies.
Oh, and be sure you do a thorough one on the firearms and ammunition.
Hey, did we tell control about Blair and Lawson?
Yes, I mean --
No.
No, I just say first phase, not completed.
Everything's fine.
Okay, just as you say.
Hi, Sue. Oh, it's you.
Calling control. Calling control.
Control to expedition 13.
Receiving you loud and clear.
Hey, it's chick city up here.
Expedition 13 to control.
First phase incomplete. Repeat, first phase --
Dutch masters.
Proceeding according to plan.
So do you save the coupons?
How do you think I got this spaceship?
Uh, fellas, I wouldn't go in there for a while if I were you.
Light a mattress on me.
Don't say anything.
Oh, hey, this is like that episode of "Here Comes the Brides"
where Candy was getting married to Jeremy
and all the women gave her a shower and then she --
Uh, Beth, don't look at my butt, please.
I think she's got a boranic device.
Yeah.
[ Humming ]
Whoa!
He's had a Fanta sweets.
Housekeeping.
I keep a --
[ Humming ]
Oh, I bet he's drooling all over -- Ugh, sheets.
[ Sniffing ]
Morning has broken.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, wow, did I --
Did I get shot to the 13th moon of Venus last night?
Ugh.
Hey, would you quit pouring so loud?
Keep that cat from stomping all around like that?
Hair of the dog.
[ Humming ]
Oh, again?
What do you think I am, Dylan Thomas?
Oh, no.
Once was enough, sister.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Humming ]
Hmm, see, Mommy likes it.
But try some saltines,
and if it stays down, you can go to school.
[ Humming ]
What was in there?
Oh, bitters, raw egg, tomato juice.
[ Coughing ]
Oh, say, lady, where's the Biffy?
[ Clears throat ]
My puka shells. Who took my puka shells?
[ Humming ]
Don't you talk?
I mute.
Process your father talks speaks English.
[ Humming ]
That is, if this isn't all a dream.
Well...
Wait, hold on. Can you lift stuff with your mind?
[ Humming ]
Maybe she's an Ellen Jamesian.
Could be.
Where's Larson?
What's going on around here?
Why were we drunk?
What color is your parachute?
[ Humming ]
Let's play the quiet game.
Well, it was getting used to this room,
but when in Rome...
I don't know how they did it,
but they came up with yet another boring scene.
The walls...
No!
But here the only sound is of the ripple
of tiny waves on the lake.
I believe that.
What's the name of the lake?
Bass Lake.
Bass Lake holds us all prisoners.
He has the power of life for death in New Atlantis.
Hey, walleyes biting?
This is New Atlantis business.
It is true.
When the continent sank beneath the sea on Earth,
my ancestors came to this planet.
It had been foreseen and planned long ago.
You have seasons here?
Yes, we have joy, we have fun, we have seasons, and you know...
At the time, it was believed that all Earth
would go beneath the water.
Like Chicago?
Seems kind of stupid now.
There are a million questions I would like to ask you.
Guess which one's first?
[ Ticking ]
The only one I can think of right now is how do I...
Make a hard-boiled egg?
We get out of here.
You're no god to us, mister.
By the Lord of Atlantis, I am yours.
Doesn't mean I have to like it, though.
Be patient, my love.
That's it?
You're mine and that's it?
Son of a gun.
Is there anything here I can't conquer?
[ Chuckles ]
Hot damn.
[ Sighs ]
Look, he's outgrown his bed.
Ah, well, what in the sand-squared's the table just moved?
Why are the bangles serving him breakfast?
Oh, look.
Daddy's got the flu again.
[ Chuckles ]
Swedish nursing team.
This is, of course, bored and thrilling, waking sweets.
That is fantastic. Fantastic.
Mm-hmm. That's good breakfast.
Mm-hmm.
Breakfast is the most boring meal of the day.
Remember that.
Ah, sweet.
You know what? You should bottle that.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay, who stole my wallet?
Okay, Peter.
[ Speaking Swedish ]
Hmm?
Amscray, beat cheeks.
What's the roll? Go long.
Get lost. Here's your hat.
I mean, go away.
Why do you want us to go away?
Just leave quietly the same way as you came in.
And nobody will get hurt.
Mm-hmm.
Where's Blair?
Process is having a discussion with Luther Blair.
Process?
Oh, good. That's just what I want to do right now.
Yeah. Is this the Hugh Hefner planet?
How do I get out of here?
You are our guest.
And a real dickweed at that.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, I see.
I stay here whether I like it or not.
We hope you like it.
Hey, look, ladies. I'm no Will Chamberlain.
Check this out.
The creature's out in the garden.
Yeah, I outdid myself. Boom!
[ Grunts ]
What is it?
Secondhand smoke, Phil.
I thought I saw something move.
Sure wasn't us.
Yeah, there is something there.
[ Grunts ]
Keeping well hidden.
It's like Rico Kasek in a union suit.
There was something there, all right.
Could it have been the girl?
What do I look like, a scientist?
I don't know.
Are we just gonna sit here and wait for Blair and Larson to come back?
That's what the script says.
What if they don't come back?
Well, we'll be sitting here anyway.
Uh...
You know my line?
We'll wait here until noon.
No!
If they haven't come back by then, we'll continue filming.
I'll say.
Hey, Phil, you want to get your butt off the equipment?
Yeah.
Maybe we'll hear something.
Yeah, maybe we'll hear that voice again.
Yeah.
Well, that didn't work.
Well, sweep the surrounding area with radar.
I'll make a cleanage.
Oh, hey, an action sequence.
[ Grunts ]
This isn't the most ideal circumstance.
I know.
Well, then we'll just wait until six.
Six, six.
We better go find Blair and Larson.
Get your guns.
Who?
Hey, hey, slow down.
Come on, where's the rush?
Come on, come on, hurry up, hurry up, come on.
Ah, good scene deserves a second run, huh?
Yep.
Sure not to miss one run of the ladder, Cy.
Whoa, fat butt coming down.
Lady with a baby.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay, let's go.
And, Cy, keep that camera rolling.
Hey, the only likable character so far.
It's Chris Jones.
[ Gasp ]
Yeah.
So, anyway, I just sat there for hours,
and Cy, Roth, get the camera rolling the whole time.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you know what I did?
I told my agent to get me a part in the film with more action.
So, after this, he signed me up for this film called "Sleep"
with Andy Warhol.
Yeah, I told my agent the same thing.
So, after this, I'm doing a film called "My Dinner with Andre."
Well, you...
Geez, the baton death march was less painful than this.
Coach.
I think it's a good idea to get a picture of the man
with the baton death march.
Coach.
I think he looks like Henry Silva.
Mm-hmm.
Look at the jawline.
Mm.
Yeah.
The eyes.
These guys are boring the heck out of me.
I'm out of here.
Here I go.
Doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo.
Hey, slow down, guys.
You're going too fast.
Hey, some morels.
And with your aid,
you Atlantis will rise stronger than ever.
Okay, you sold me.
I'm not giving you insurance.
Poor Luther Blair, a drink, my daughter.
You know, someday we're gonna have to learn
how to feed ourselves.
Breakfast with Carl Sandburg.
Come, Luther Blair.
Refresh yourself.
Say yes, yes to Martini and Rossier on the rocks.
Oh, what was that?
Was that a plot point?
Did something happen?
What?
What a day.
Oh, Queen of Atlantis.
Grandma.
Let this be a day of rejoicing.
Did you switch the poisons yet?
Good.
How would you like to see under my smock?
Tomorrow we begin thinking of the creature's destruction.
Right now I'm thinking of MD 2020.
It's the wine of the century, you know.
Ah, sweet delicious fools.
Yes.
Once again, you Atlantis shall rule.
I am so toasted right now.
Once more we shall, ah, I'm come, Elizabeth, regain our...
Oh, my.
Tip O'Neill, ladies and gentlemen.
Tip O'Neill.
Wait, did you poison your dad just so we could go on a date?
Hey, I just got it.
They're being followed by this monster.
Do you fellows see a barbecued mime back there?
Well, it was right here yesterday.
Well, it could be too identical to see somewhere else.
Yeah, it could be, but I doubt it.
We followed the same trail from the beacon.
See if the entrance isn't sealed.
You come all this way here and you find a...
Ah, close.
Oh, my.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no way.
No crack, nothing.
What is it?
What is he making a lean to back there?
Hi.
Brought you fellows a cake.
You like sponge?
No, I couldn't be.
Oh, shit.
Well, I guess that's his way of saying hi.
I'll rush it from the fire.
No.
No, we better all stick together.
Hold your fire.
We'll try and scare him away.
By firing at him.
Ah, you tried that one before.
Well, I wet him, you.
Okay, let him have it.
Oh, I bet this monster turns out to be good.
The bullets have no effect.
I'll try a gas grenade.
Gas grenade?
Are you thinking...
Ah.
Geez, I'm trying to spice up your movie and suddenly I'm the jerk.
Girl.
Let's get out of here.
Yeah, that scene was almost exciting.
Let's go back to the ship and sit around.
No, no, not with the stranger in paradise again.
I don't know why.
Beautiful name.
Do you think I've traveled millions of miles through space to find you?
We'll make the incisions here and here.
It was foretold in the sands of time that you would meet.
We'll get a larcen and find a way to escape and you're coming with me.
The hills have eyes, eyes, eyes.
Yes, my love.
How do we get to the entrance?
Practice.
The entrance is sealed.
There is no escape from New Atlantis until...
Until process gives his consent.
Miss Bytes, I'm out of here.
He will never do that.
Even for you, his daughter?
We are all his daughters under the law of Atlantis.
All women look to the ruler of Atlantis as their father.
Dear God, he's unappealing.
There's no other way out of here.
Atlantis is impregnable.
But I'm not.
Whoever desires to enter or leave will be destroyed at the boundaries.
Thus, the need for the destruction of the creature.
Oh, like there's a plot to this.
I will be back the hour of sunset.
I'm waiting for my kiss.
I'm going to go take the first in a series of cold showers.
I don't think you're supposed to be in here.
Hey, Joel, look over here.
Hey, quit trying to distract me, Tom.
I'm trying to watch you move.
Walk to Orson.
Orson.
Blair?
Brown?
Underwood.
Orson.
John.
Blair!
Blair, the moment I met you, I swear.
What's the first stud finder?
Notice it doesn't point to him.
Hey, we've been walking for hours.
Yeah, well, we've been watching for hours.
Whoa, put your shoes back on.
It smells like mummy meat.
What is it?
Look back.
Number three, the lodge.
This is it.
The end of the class.
We're going to go on the other side.
Oh.
Hey, climb that tree, Anderson.
Oh, me?
Yeah, you.
Obviously, I'm elected again.
Yeah, we better see what's there.
Hey, come on.
You're not supposed to be in here
and you're distracting me.
Hey, Joe, look who's in the theater over here.
What? I don't...
Tom, come on.
I know the movie's bad, but quit clowning around.
Hey, these guys will go to great lengths
to avoid green speeds.
God.
Not so loud.
What else did you see?
There's nothing else.
Come on down, Stanhope.
Charles, Joseph, Stanhope,
you come down from there this instant.
Come on down.
Don't worry, we'll film every minute of it.
So I said to him, you have to stop it
or you're going to have heart problems.
He didn't need to say that to me, but...
Whoa, suddenly it's gym class around here.
Guys, does the word heaven mean anything to you?
It's like a beer commercial.
Guys, there's nothing up there.
Hey, I'm going to go take a walk by myself
for a while, all alone, okay?
Beautiful, gorgeous.
A species of fauna that demands
the most extensive research program.
You mean different to all this?
My dear Anderson, fauna, or in this case faunae,
refers to the animals characteristic of the region.
All right, suddenly it's British.
A man and a woman
have sometimes been referred to as an animal.
You mean people.
Girls!
Hey, why didn't you say so before?
If you two are going to argue about it,
we'll never get over that wall.
We've got to find some way to scale it.
We could get on each other's shoulders.
I'll get on top and if the girls get down...
Hey, not too high.
Cut down that sapling and lean it against the wall.
That'll do it.
Well, go on, go on.
We do have fun.
Dad, the three stooges are here to see you.
Dad?
Tonight on Music Through the Night,
sweet for a drunken dad.
Oh, that was riveting.
Oh, you again? Listen, I'm getting sick of you
and you're really starting to wear out your welcome.
I know what you mean, Tom.
You know, everyone in this film is starting to wear out their welcome.
That's not what I meant.
Just... just...
I'm going to ignore you.
Just leave me alone, okay?
Easy, easy.
Sit it down there.
Let it fall the rest of the way.
I think the tree should be fuller this Christmas.
Moses.
The creatures!
There's only a tree that fell down.
Look, nothing can get over the wall, not even the creatures.
Well, anyway, Debbie's got this eye shadow.
Ow!
Hey, cut that out!
I'll never get over that wall with some sort of an electrical charge guarding it.
That's for sure.
Well, if not over the wall and not around the wall,
why not that under the wall?
Hey.
Why not?
Why not, indeed?
You're a genius, honey. I could kiss you.
Peter Mundo, not...
Oh, I'm warning you.
Stay over there.
You're still on hold?
Control calling Expedition 13.
Calling Expedition 13.
Come in, 13.
If you'd like to make a call, please hang up and try again.
If you'd like to make a call...
Where are the savings?
Well, we mustn't be discouraged.
Shut up.
There are many reasons for not hearing from them.
Yeah.
Atmospheric conditions.
Uh-huh.
Being away from their base of operations.
Uh, did I mention atmospheric conditions yet?
We don't begin to think of.
Yes, but they were given orders to keep us fully informed.
Ow, ow! Stop it! Knock it off!
Stop it, stop it! Ow!
My eyes.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(HUMMING)
Watch this.
Watch it.
Mary Sue, you split left.
Jill, do a slant left and hut hut.
(SCREAMS)
Oh!
All right!
Hey, somebody finally filled my dream!
Oh, I hate Hell Week.
Yes, Ty... Ow!
You're really pushing it, mister.
Warning you.
Stay over there.
Look, all I said was, "Deb might dye her hair."
Ow, ow!
Not that does it.
I'm coming to you, you dannit, miss Al.
Oh, it's Al with the ding-a-dong.
Hey, Tom, what the hell?
Hey, you didn't tell us Tommy was in here.
Is that Tommy?
You're not supposed to be in the theater, you know.
Hey!
All I want you to knock it off.
There's no wrong person in here.
I'm telling you.
Help!
(SOBBING)
Joe, I think Timmy is trying to kill Tom Servo.
Yeah, that's right.
Go to the bridge.
Stay frosty.
I've got a plan, OK?
All right, come on.
Come on, we're coming, Savannah!
(GROANING)
Kill me.
Kill-- oh, say, Crow, could you please kill me?
I'm the teensiest bit busy, Tom.
I'm getting to it.
Oh, OK.
I'm not trying to tell you how to do your job,
but make sure you hit the right one.
Oh, stop kibbitzing.
Come on, man.
Drink the redcoats are coming.
Let go of him, you bitch.
Ah!
Stay close, Newt.
Did I mention I want you to kill me?
Oh, Tom, would you shut up with you?
It's not always one thing or another.
Oh, OK, Crow.
Now, listen, I'm going to try to--
ah, blow the hatch, OK?
I'm three, all right?
Ah!
All right, one, two--
Hey, don't kill me.
Sure could go for a sandwich.
Oh, shut up, Tom.
Three!
Ah!
Ow!
Quick!
Give me rocket number nine!
Warning.
So, listen, I don't want you to ever--
I mean, never let a dark specter onto the ship again.
I don't even care if he's shaped like me.
What were you thinking?
Oh, don't hit or yell.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't stay mad at you.
Hey, look, you know what that means?
Commercial sign.
You feel like a commercial sign, huh, Hubble?
I'll say, uh, if you two are done over there,
I'd really appreciate it if you could kill me now.
Oh, we're going to kill you, all right.
Yeah, come on.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHTER]
Everything's OK.
It worked out.
We're the firemen's couldn't be prouder.
If you can't hear us, we'll yell in louder.
Join campfire girls and become our leader.
Ricker, racker, fire-racker, shoo-boom-bah.
Bugs, bunny, bugs, bunny, rah, rah, rah.
Rah, rah, rah.
When slumber parties go bad.
Funny thing, she's the RA.
This is tough.
Oh, no, not liturgical dance, no.
Ah, nice move.
Whoa.
[APPLAUSE]
Oh, that's fun.
Firewalk with me.
Whatever Lola wants, Lola gets, for at all that Broadway rhythm.
[WHISTLING]
[HUMMING]
All right, roll the shoulders, and roll the shoulders,
and sway the hips, and that's good.
Kick turn, two kick.
Oh, I love it.
[LAUGHS]
Forward shoulder, shimmy an arm, stretch and double back down,
and hip.
This is what happens when you send your kids
to an all-girls school.
Oh.
Stand for fight.
Stand for a fight.
And now, let's cheer it for the Kingsford dancers.
Kingsford girls, light quickly.
The carry-on fire, the god of sun is angered.
His daughter has violated his law.
The code of Atlantis says the eldest daughter
must be married first.
Hey, you want to crack a window?
The god of sun has passed judgment.
At the first ray of light, you must die.
She must die.
I think I just said that.
Your butt's showing.
We captured them in the garden.
Make them watch the sacrifice.
Let all the men watch the sacrifice.
Yes.
Get over them.
That's right, and now the spanking.
The spanking.
Spank me.
Ah, I have to tinkle, sir.
Where's Blair and Lawson?
Prisoners in their chambers.
Thank you, girls.
That was terrific.
Get ready for the bridesmaid number.
[laughs]
Ah, forget it.
Time for a smoke.
You know, as always, the answer's tobacco.
Huh.
Johnny Longcrunch.
True.
You know, maybe if you told us what you were trying to find,
we could help.
Huh?
Honey, I'm a genius.
I love me.
I could kiss me.
Oh, son of a gun.
I found the Murphy bed.
Now, you know women can do that, but men can't.
Oh, I've seen that trick.
It's a hell of a lot of logical.
All right.
What was I thinking with that whole doorknob thing?
And now, ladies and gentlemen, another boring 20-minute scene.
Hey, how come no girls are here to tie me up when I walk through here?
Huh?
[music playing]
Sigh, you getting all this?
Good.
Oscar.
I wasn't dreaming about the fire maintenance.
Blair.
God.
Listen to me.
I want you to stop touching yourself.
Hey.
Try the chair by the wall.
In front of you.
Move.
You said go to the chair by the wall, and I'm the jerk?
Push it.
The exit is there.
Hurry.
Hunt.
I believe.
Oh, I never thought I'd see you again.
Got to get out of here.
Yep.
Sure did open that trap door.
No need to see it.
Oh.
Huh?
She's got legs.
Oh, you see, Sigh just fainted, and they didn't even know he was filming this.
Loved the camera on the floor.
[music playing]
Music really matches the action.
It does.
Here come the brides of color.
Oh.
Next, the girls were whisked away on a man-kept shopping spree.
Hey, you were right.
That was fun.
Yep.
That's right, folks.
More shots of us coming on through.
Save your strength.
The cords grow tighter if you struggle.
What are they going to do with us?
You are safe.
They will not harm you.
But if that's true, why are we tied?
I think we're going to witness an ancient ritual, a sacrifice to one of their gods.
Bingo.
The god of sun has been angered.
He must be appeased.
I could go for peas right now.
Wait a minute.
You smell roasting girl?
Hey, more boring scenes this way.
What's the matter with him?
What?
Oh, Hestia switched drinks with him earlier.
Hestia?
Oh, the girl.
Well, that's what happened to me.
Right.
Now guns ought to be around here someplace.
If only we had a door now.
So I said to Jill, you really shouldn't wear that rouge, and so now she's mad because...
Huh?
He's gone.
The only man who's gone.
Go back to the flag.
Oh, so now they go back again.
Polonios?
I've got them.
Oh, plot convenience playhouse presents.
What plot?
Convenience warehouse.
Look, it's almost morning.
We hurry up and get back to the ship.
Have to find Hestia first.
What do we need her for?
I promise to take her with us.
Oh, I see.
Well, what do you mean by that crap?
Take it back.
We need her help to get out of here.
We need Hestia.
I'll follow you.
You seem to know what you're doing.
Hey everybody, remember me?
I think you forgot I was part of this film here.
I'm telling you, he's going to turn out to be a hero.
Philippe has strayed too far from the ocean and is drying up.
Well, not for that guy.
Now back to more boring scenes.
Snipe, here's Snipe.
Guys, I couldn't find any Snipe.
Guys.
Oh no, Dad's waking up.
Oh, I'm back on Atlantis where I'm the god of everything.
Yeah.
You know, I've got a headache this big and it's got cyber-auth went all over it.
Ah!
Take down, take down, two points, take down, take down, two points.
I'm just a girl who can't say no and I'm in a terrible fix.
I'm so cold.
And now right here on our stage we have the wonderful Patrice Munsell with the "Campfire Girls" dance.
Oh yes, always a favorite.
Everybody in with this crowd.
Everybody was kung fu fighting.
Kill me now.
Addis and Stephen are doing some weird stuff over there.
Does anybody have a copy of "Final Exit" with them? I'm gonna need it.
Oh, "Ceeley, Posturepedic Morning."
Oh, keep away, keep away.
Ah, nooner.
Well, this is a lot better. That last scene had way too much action for me.
Listen.
Yeah, voice, music, but which way?
And why weren't we invited?
Okay now, come on girls, get into your sleeping bags. No more sacrifices tonight. Come on.
Ah, I hate modern dance.
"While a Tharp Must Die."
She's a heckler. They hate hecklers.
Hello ladies.
Yeah, good. If you get near a consonant, let us know, will ya?
Could I get some service over here?
I'm the god of hellfire.
"Pattend of 50's Scream."
He's a cute one.
Excuse me, sir. The show's already started. You'll have to wait until the middle of the third...
How to pick up women.
Oh, I'm such a bad actress.
Something smells really good.
Mmm.
Damn! Awesome! Thanks, I've found this!
Kill it!
For Pete, take a shot at it!
Alright!
Oh, hi guys!
Rollercoaster!
Blob, blob!
Say what?
Oh, Mississippi 2, Mississippi 3, Mississippi...
I'm going to bounce off him!
Rollercast grenade!
Oh, you remember this one, guys?
Yep.
Here comes...
Ha ha ha!
It's fun.
Oh, now he's really going to be overcooked.
A change in the menu ducks off.
Thanks for hurling that gas bomb at me.
Aw, darling, have you been smoking?
Ooh, you're running a temp!
Oh no, not Stranger in Paradise again!
Even I'm tired of it.
I'll never fail you, Estia.
That is her name, isn't it honey?
Doesn't she worry about underarm on her?
No.
Sure.
I hate to pull rank on you, but...
It's not rejoice too soon, we still have to get out of this place.
No!
The fighting process doesn't stop us.
Estia will help us.
I'll stop process.
Oh, sorry, Estia, sorry about the sacrifice there.
We were just kidding, honey.
We all signed it up.
I think you'll like the campus.
We have everything you need.
I'm sure you'll all recognize this lovely melody,
"A Stranger in Paradise".
But did you know its original title was
"The Palefepsy and Dance Number Two" by Borodin?
Come on.
The answer split? Everyone saw?
Your father process is dead.
Heikeba!
You are our new ruler.
Hail to Estia, Queen of Atlantis.
Long live the Queen.
Hey, a moment ago you were roasting my butt.
I know who I've been loving to earth, but I shall return.
Meanwhile, Nisa shall be your temporary ruler.
Nisa, who didn't do a dance to sacrifice me.
What about us?
I give not a crap for thee.
You need live in fear no longer.
But process, he promised his husband.
We'll be sending expeditions from the earth.
I may come back myself.
Don't worry, girls, I'll be back and take care of the situation.
I can barely hear my heartbeat.
Hey, please, girls, one at a time.
Just your names.
I have the facts.
Sigh, Roth, shame on you.
Mm.
Wait a minute.
These guys are married.
I call foul.
Who?
Oh, I really don't care if I do have a boyfriend.
You know me.
Vina mundo.
Okay, ladies first.
Goodbye.
Thanks for the valium.
Yo, honey, this is where the first half of the film took place, pretty much.
Yeah, but they'll probably make her a stewardess, right?
Yeah, just like them.
Ain't that a man?
Anderson, you make windows.
Contact control.
Aye, aye, skipper.
Captain Larson.
You bite me.
You handle the take-off.
Aye, aye, sir.
Calling control.
Hey, what's the message?
The message is hot steamin' love, Texas style.
Mission complete.
Done up nice.
Attempting re-entry.
Mm-hmm.
Was that a bit harsh?
Oh, boy.
I don't think it was harsh for you.
It's been a big day.
Is that harsh?
What a day.
Oh, I get it.
Hey, you don't have to be Freud to figure that one out.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, no, no.
Take it easy, you guys.
You just got to say to yourself, it's only a movie.
It's only a movie.
If I could just make sense of it in my own mind, I could--
[MUMBLING]
Oh, come on, Tom.
Just let it out.
Talk about it.
You'll feel better.
Go ahead.
OK, let's see here.
Secretary took a long walk downstairs.
Mm-hmm.
Officer and menish women sit down for a while.
Right.
Astronauts sit around for a while.
Uh-huh.
Cut back to officers and menish women.
They sit around for a while.
Come on.
Cut back to astronauts.
They sit around for a while.
Oh, boy.
Cut back to officers and menish women.
They're still sitting around.
Right.
Cut back to astronauts.
They're still sitting around.
Oh, that's OK, Tom.
Take it easy.
At least you tried to talk about it.
Come on, crew.
I'm sure you can make sense out of this movie.
I'll try, Joel.
Let's see.
Astronauts land on planet and run.
Right.
And keep on running and running and running and running.
Then three of the astronauts go back to the ship.
Right.
And sit around for a while.
Cut back to officers and menish women sitting around.
Come back to astronauts.
They're still sitting around.
Right, right.
That's OK.
OK, my little botsies have been through so much today,
what with Crow accepting that dark specter into his heart
and then forcing the rest of us to go through all the time.
OK, I got it.
All right.
Well, you know what?
Listen, I got an idea.
I've got a really cute letter here that we can read.
And then it'll cheer us all up.
So let's put that on still store,
Cambot, and put the other side on still store.
Good.
OK, this one says, "Dear MST 3000,
my name is Ashley Holtgraver, and I love your show.
And in the last few days, I've been noticing how much
little sister and Crow look alike."
Here is a picture.
"Even though Crow is better looking, they sound the same.
My brother is slowly turning into Tom Serbo."
Here's another picture.
"I want to know if you are cloning."
Oh, that's cute.
Yeah, that's really nice, Ashley.
Thanks a lot.
I feel better.
Yeah, see, we made it through, Mads.
Yeah, throw us your worst will. We can handle it.
Mighty Jack Castle of Boo Man Q.
He's a cake.
Fugitive alien, bellcats.
Go ahead, do your worst. We can take it, huh?
Yeah, even fire mains from outer space.
The poison wine! What was the point of the poison wine?
Cy-ron had to plan the film just so we could get to the parts
that had more patties.
Listen, sirs, I hope you're proud.
Proud doesn't begin to cover it, Booby.
As a matter of fact, Frank and I went to--
Oh, Frank.
Yes, that's very nice, Frank.
As I was saying, Joel, your reaction to the--
[screaming]
Frank, no! My God!
Who are you?
[music playing]
[music continues]
[music ends]
[knocking]